A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller, Vice Presidential records xFA250
Rockefeller Archive Center
- National Commission on Water Quality, 1973-1977; 9; 56 Cubic Feet 56 record cartons
  - Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Residuals Coefficients - Resgen Module (Box 39, Folder 1211)
  - Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - OBERS Projections: Economic Activity in the United States, 1929-2020, U.S. Water Resources Council, September 1972 (Box 39, Folder 1212)
  - Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - OBERS Projections: Population and Personal Income, U.S. Water Resources Council, March 1974 (Box 39, Folder 1213)
  - Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Program Specifications: SEAS Extensions to Inter-Industry Forecasting Model, Report to EPA, by Control Data (1 of 2), February 1974 (Box 39, Folder 1214)
  - Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Program Specifications: SEAS Extensions to Inter-Industry Forecasting Model, Report to EPA, by Control Data (2 of 2), February 1974 (Box 39, Folder 1215)
  - Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Capital Markets and Water Quality Needs: 1975-1985, by The Conference Board, July 1975 (Box 40, Folder 1216)
  - Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Distribution of Water Pollution Control Costs, Draft, by Urban Systems Research and Engineering, December 1975 (Box 40, Folder 1217)
  - Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Distribution of Water Pollution Control Costs, Vol. I, by Urban Systems Research and Engineering, March 1976 (Box 40, Folder 1218)
  - Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Distribution of Water Pollution Control Costs, Vol. II, by Urban Systems Research and Engineering, March 1976 (Box 40, Folder 1219)
  - Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Developing a 50-State Model for Forecasting the Fiscal Situation for State-Local Governments, Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations, July 1974 (Box 40, Folder 1220)
  - Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Financing PL92-500: A Study of State and Local Government Budgets, Vol. I, by Data Resources, October 1975 (Box 40, Folder 1221)
  - Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Financing PL92-500: A Study of State and Local Government Budgets, Vol. II, by Data Resources, October 1975 (Box 40, Folder 1222)
  - Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Financing PL92-500: A Study of State and Local Government Budgets, Vol. III, by Data Resources, October 1975 (Box 40, Folder 1223)
  - Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Financing PL92-500: The Impact of the Federal Water Pollution Control Act of 1972 on the Municipal Bond Market (Draft), by Data Resources, September 1975 (Box 40, Folder 1224)
  - Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Financing PL92-500: Vol. II (Draft), by Data Resources, September 1975 (Box 40, Folder 1225)
  - Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Financing PL92-500: Appendix (Draft), by Data Resources, September 1975 (Box 40, Folder 1226)
  - Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Financing PL92-500: Vol. I (Summary of Reports), by Data Resources, August 1975 (Box 40, Folder 1227)
  - Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Municipal Choice of Options for Meeting Effluent Limitations and Goals (Draft), by Meta Systems, July 1975 (Box 40, Folder 1228)
  - Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Municipal Choice Among Waste Treatment Options, by Meta Systems, December 1975 (Box 40, Folder 1229)
  - Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Irrigation Return Flows and Pollutant Run-off from Nonirrigated Agriculture (Draft), by the Center for Agricultural and Rural Development, Iowa State University, July 1975 (Box 40, Folder 1230)
  - Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Irrigation Return Flows and Pollutant Run-off from Nonirrigated Agriculture, Final Report, Center for Agricultural and Rural Development, Iowa State University, July 1975 (Box 40, Folder 1231)
  - Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Analysis of the Agricultural Impacts Study by Iowa State University, by Management Science Systems, August 1975 (Box 40, Folder 1232)
  - Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Effects of Effluent Discharge Limitations on Foreign Trade (Draft), by Public Research Institute, June 1975 (Box 40, Folder 1233)
  - Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Effects of Effluent Discharge Limitations on Foreign Trade (Final Report), by Public Research Institute, February 1976 (Box 40, Folder 1234)
  - Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Impact on Residential Property Prices of Future Levels of Water Quality (Draft) by David M. Dornbusch and Co., May 1975 (Box 41, Folder 1235)
  - Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Impact of Water Quality Improvements on Residential Property Prices, by David M. Dornbusch and Co., December 1975 (Box 41, Folder 1236)
  - Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Water Related Recreation Benefits from PL92-500, Vol. I, by National Planning Association, November 1975 (Box 41, Folder 1237)
  - Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Water Related Recreation Benefits from PL92-500, Vol. II, by National Planning Association, November 1975 (Box 41, Folder 1238)
  - Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Water Related Recreation Benefits from PL92-500, Appendices, by National Planning Association, November 1975 (Box 41, Folder 1239)
  - Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Benefits to Commercial and Recreational Fisheries from Quality of Coastal Waters, Vol. I (Draft), by Florida State University, July 1975 (Box 41, Folder 1240)
  - Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Benefits to Commercial and Recreational Fisheries from Quality of Coastal Waters, Vol. II (Draft), by Florida State University, July 1975 (Box 41, Folder 1241)
  - Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Benefits from Water Pollution Abatement, Coastal Waters, Vol. I, by Florida State University, April 1976 (Box 41, Folder 1242)
  - Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Benefits from Water Pollution Abatement, Coastal Waters, Vol. II, by Florida State University, April 1976 (Box 41, Folder 1243)
  - Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Water Quality Improvements on Public Swimming (Draft), by Battelle Memorial Institute, July 1975 (Box 41, Folder 1244)
  - Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Benefits from Water Pollution Abatement: Beach Closings and Reopenings, by Battelle Memorial Institute, February 1976 (Box 41, Folder 1245)
  - Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Lake Washington-Lake Union: Social Impact Study (Draft), by Human Resources Planning Institute, June 1975 (Box 41, Folder 1246)
  - Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Social Impacts of PL92-500, by Human Resources Planning Institute, December 1975 (Box 41, Folder 1247)
  - Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Summary of the Social Impact Studies, by Human Resources Planning Institute, January 1976 (Box 41, Folder 1248)
  - Other Papers - Not NCWQ Documents - Effluent Charges: Papers by Susan Rose-Ackerman (September 1975), Otto Davis (June 1976), Gardner Brown (August 1975) and Allan Kneese (August 1975) (Box 42, Folder 1249)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Boston Harbor/Charles River (Draft), by Process Research, June 1975 (Box 42, Folder 1250)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Boston Harbor/Charles River, Environmental Research & Technology, April 1976 (Box 42, Folder 1251)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Connecticut River Basin, by the Center for the Environment and Man, April 1975 (Box 42, Folder 1252)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Housatonic River (Draft), by Lawler, Matusky and Skelly Engineers, June 1975 (Box 42, Folder 1253)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Housatonic River (Final Report), by Lawler, Matusky and Skelly Engineers (1 of 2), December 1975 (Box 42, Folder 1254)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Housatonic River (Final Report), by Lawler, Matusky and Skelly Engineers (2 of 2), December 1975 (Box 42, Folder 1255)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Potomac River (Draft), Academy of Natural Sciences of Philadelphia, July 1975 (Box 42, Folder 1256)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Potomac River (Final Report), by the Academy of Natural Sciences of Philadelphia, July 1975 (Box 42, Folder 1257)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Potomac Estuary (Draft), by GKY and Associates, January 1975 (Box 42, Folder 1258)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Potomac Estuary (Final Report), by GKY and Associates, January 1975 (Box 42, Folder 1259)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Saint John River, Maine (Draft), by Meta Systems, April 1975 (Box 42, Folder 1260)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Saint John River, Maine, by Meta Systems (1 of 2), December 1975 (Box 42, Folder 1261)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Saint John River, Maine, by Meta Systems (2 of 2), December 1975 (Box 42, Folder 1262)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Susquehanna River, Final Report, Lawler, Matusky, and Skelly Engineers (1 of 2), December 1975 (Box 42, Folder 1263)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Susquehanna River, Final Report, Lawler, Matusky, and Skelly Engineers (2 of 2), December 1975 (Box 43, Folder 1264)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Chesapeake Bay, Vol. I, Water Quality, by Virginia Institute of Marine Science, June 1975 (Box 43, Folder 1265)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Chesapeake Bay, Vol. II, Ecological Conditions, by Virginia Institute of Marine Science, June 1975 (Box 43, Folder 1266)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Escambia River and Bay, Florida, Executive Summary Draft, by Atlantis Scientific, May 1975 (Box 43, Folder 1267)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Escambia River and Bay, Florida, Draft, by Atlantis Scientific, May 1975 (Box 43, Folder 1268)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Escambia River and Bay, Florida, Final Report, by Atlantis Scientific, May 1976 (Box 43, Folder 1269)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Mississippi-Minnesota-St. Croix Confluences, Draft, Midwest Research Institute, May 1975 (Box 43, Folder 1270)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Mississippi-Minnesota-St. Croix Confluences, by Midwest Research Institute, March 1976 (Box 43, Folder 1271)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Upper Mississippi River Basin, Final Report, by Water Resources Engineers, July 1975 (Box 43, Folder 1272)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Santee River Basin, Draft, by Academy of Natural Sciences of Philadelphia, July 1975 (Box 43, Folder 1273)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Santee River Basin, Final Report, by Academy of Natural Sciences of Philadelphia, July 1975 (Box 43, Folder 1274)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Santee River Basin, Section II: Final Report, by Water Resources Engineers, April 1975 (Box 43, Folder 1275)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Trinity River Basin, Draft, by Water Resources Engineers, May 1975 (Box 43, Folder 1276)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Trinity River Basin, by Water Resources Engineers, May 1976 (Box 43, Folder 1277)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Yadkin-Pee Dee River Basin, by TRW Transportation and Environmental Operations, May 1975 (Box 43, Folder 1278)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Iowa-Cedar Rivers Basin, Draft, by Midwest Research Institute, May 1975 (Box 44, Folder 1279)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Iowa-Cedar Rivers Basin, by Midwest Research Institute, March 1976 (Box 44, Folder 1280)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Iowa-Cedar Rivers Basin, Section II: Final Report, by Water Resources Engineers, July 1975 (Box 44, Folder 1281)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Lower Missouri River, Draft, by Midwest Research Institute, June 1975 (Box 44, Folder 1282)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Lower Missouri River, Final Report, by Midwest Research Institute, December 1975 (Box 44, Folder 1283)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Guadalupe-San Antonio River Basin, Draft, Water Resources Engineers, May 1975 (Box 44, Folder 1284)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Guadalupe-San Antonio River Basin, by Water Resources Engineers, March 1976 (Box 44, Folder 1285)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - South Platte River, Draft, by Tetra Tech, May 1975 (Box 44, Folder 1286)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - South Platte River, by Tetra Tech, December 1975 (Box 44, Folder 1287)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Upper Rio Grande, Section II: Studies, Final Report, by Water Resources Engineers, March 1975 (Box 44, Folder 1288)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Upper Rio Grande, Draft, by the Academy of Natural Sciences of Philadelphia, June 1975 (Box 44, Folder 1289)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Upper Rio Grande, Final Report, by the Academy of Natural Sciences of Philadelphia, June 1975 (Box 44, Folder 1290)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Alaska, Gulf of, Draft, by Tetra Tech, May 1975 (Box 44, Folder 1291)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Alaska, Gulf of, Final Report, by Tetra Tech, February 1976 (Box 45, Folder 1292)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Lower Columbia River, Draft, by Tetra Tech, February 1975 (Box 45, Folder 1293)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Lower Columbia River, Final Report, by Tetra Tech, February 1976 (Box 45, Folder 1294)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Columbia River, Draft, by Parametrix, May 1975 (Box 45, Folder 1295)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Columbia River, Final Report, by Parametrix (1 of 2), December 1975 (Box 45, Folder 1296)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Columbia River, Final Report, by Parametrix (2 of 2), December 1975 (Box 45, Folder 1297)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Hawaii, Draft, by Tetra Tech, May 1975 (Box 45, Folder 1298)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Hawaii, Final Report, by Tetra Tech, February 1976 (Box 45, Folder 1299)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Puerto Rico, Draft, by Tetra Tech, May 1975 (Box 45, Folder 1300)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Puerto Rico, Final Report, by Tetra Tech, February 1976 (Box 45, Folder 1301)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Snake River, Idaho, Draft, by Tetra Tech, February 1975 (Box 45, Folder 1302)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Snake River, Idaho, Final Report, by Tetra Tech, February 1976 (Box 45, Folder 1303)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Snake River, Draft, by Parametrix, April 1975 (Box 45, Folder 1304)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Snake River, Final Report, by Parametrix, January 1976 (Box 45, Folder 1305)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Southern California Bight, Draft, by Tetra Tech, May 1975 (Box 45, Folder 1306)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Southern California Bight, Final Report, by Tetra Tech, February 1976 (Box 45, Folder 1307)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Biscayne Bay (Draft), Water Resources Engineers, May 1975 (Box 45, Folder 1308)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Biscayne Bay (Final Report), Water Resources Engineers, March 1976 (Box 45, Folder 1309)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Hudson River (Draft), Lawler, Matusky and Skilly Engineers, (1 of 4) Chapters I-III, August 1975 (Box 46, Folder 1310)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Hudson River (Draft), Lawler, Matusky and Skilly Engineers, (2 of 4) Chapters IV-VIII, August 1975 (Box 46, Folder 1311)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Hudson River (Draft), Lawler, Matusky and Skilly Engineers, (3 of 4) Chapters IX-XI, August 1975 (Box 46, Folder 1312)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Hudson River (Draft), Lawler, Matusky and Skilly Engineers, (4 of 4) Chapters XII-XIII, August 1975 (Box 46, Folder 1313)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Hudson River (Final Report), Lawler, Matusky and Skilly Engineers, (1 of 4) Chapters I-III, March 1976 (Box 46, Folder 1314)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Hudson River (Final Report), Lawler, Matusky and Skilly Engineers, (2 of 4) Chapters IV-X, March 1976 (Box 46, Folder 1315)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Hudson River (Final Report), Lawler, Matusky and Skilly Engineers, (3 of 4) Chapters XI, March 1976 (Box 46, Folder 1316)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Hudson River (Final Report), Lawler, Matusky and Skilly Engineers, (4 of 4) Chapters XII-XIII, March 1976 (Box 46, Folder 1317)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Percy Priest Reservoir (Final Report), Vanderbilt University, August 1975 (Box 46, Folder 1318)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - St. John's River/Estuary (Exec. Summary, Draft), Atlantis Scientific, May 1975 (Box 46, Folder 1319)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - St. John's River/Estuary (Draft), Atlantis Scientific, May 1975 (Box 46, Folder 1320)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - St. John's River/Estuary (Final Report), Atlantis Scientific, March 1976 (Box 46, Folder 1321)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Utah Lake/Jordan River (Draft), Environmental Dynamics, August 1975 (Box 46, Folder 1322)
  - Environmental Studies: River Reaches - Utah Lake/Jordan River (Final Report), Environmental Dynamics, December 1975 (Box 46, Folder 1323)
  - Overall Studies - Municipal Wastewaters in Open Coastal Waters (Draft), Southern California Coastal Water Research Project, August 1975 (Box 46, Folder 1324)
  - Overall Studies - Municipal Wastewaters in Open Coastal Waters (Final Report), Southern California Coastal Water Research Project, December 1975 (Box 46, Folder 1325)
  - Overall Studies - Disposal of Wastewater Residuals, Vol. 1 of 2, Environmental Quality Systems, March 1976 (Box 46, Folder 1326)
  - Overall Studies - Disposal of Wastewater Residuals, Vol. 2 of 2, Environmental Quality Systems, March 1976 (Box 46, Folder 1327)
  - Overall Studies - Water Quality Evaluations, Hydroscience, December 1975 (Box 46, Folder 1328)
  - Overall Studies - Compliance Monitoring (Draft), Energy Resources, June 1975 (Box 46, Folder 1329)
  - Overall Studies - Construction Grants (Draft), Touche Ross, April 1975 (Box 47, Folder 1330)
  - Overall Studies - Construction Grants (Final Report), Touche Ross, August 1975 (Box 47, Folder 1331)
  - Overall Studies - Enforcement (Draft), Environmental Law Institute, April 1975 (Box 47, Folder 1332)
  - Overall Studies - Enforcement (Final Report), Environmental Law Institute, July 1975 (Box 47, Folder 1333)
  - Overall Studies - Pollution Discharge Elimination System (Permit System) (Draft), Energy and Environmental Analysis, May 1975 (Box 47, Folder 1334)
  - Overall Studies - Pollution Discharge Elimination System (Permit System) (Final Report), Energy and Environmental Analysis, undated (Box 47, Folder 1335)
  - Overall Studies - Planning Requirements (Draft), by Harold F. Wise, May 1975 (Box 47, Folder 1336)
  - Overall Studies - Planning Requirements (Final Report), by Harold F. Wise, August 1975 (Box 47, Folder 1337)
  - Overall Studies - Study Design, Elizabeth Haskell, 1974 (Box 47, Folder 1338)
  - Overall Studies - Attitudes of Selected Groups (Draft), Oregon Research Institute, August 1975 (Box 47, Folder 1339)
  - Overall Studies - Attitudes of Participants (Final Report), Oregon Research Institute, December 1975 (Box 47, Folder 1340)
  - Overall Studies - Problems of Agriculture "Doers" (Draft), David Hartley and Victoria Price, July 1975 (Box 47, Folder 1341)
  - Overall Studies - Problems of Agriculture "Doers" (Final Report), David Hartley and Victoria Price, September 1975 (Box 48, Folder 1342)
  - Overall Studies - Problems of Municipal "Doers" (Draft), Victoria Price and David Hartley, July 1975 (Box 48, Folder 1343)
  - Overall Studies - Problems of Municipal "Doers" (Final Report), Victoria Price and David Hartley, September 1975 (Box 48, Folder 1344)
  - Overall Studies - Problems of Industrial "Doers" (Draft), Phillip Clark, July 1975 (Box 48, Folder 1345)
  - Overall Studies - Legal Issues, Environmental and Safety Research Services, September 1975 (Box 48, Folder 1346)
  - Overall Studies - Legal Issues: Tables and Appendices, Environmental and Safety Research Services, September 1975 (Box 48, Folder 1347)
  - Overall Studies - Public Participation (Draft), by James Ragan Associates, June 1975 (Box 48, Folder 1348)
  - Overall Studies - Public Participation (Final Report), by James Ragan Associates, September 1975 (Box 48, Folder 1349)
  - Regional Reports - Delaware River Basin (Phase One Report), Betz Environmental Engineers, January 1975 (Box 48, Folder 1350)
  - Regional Reports - Delaware River Basin (Draft, Vol. I), Betz Environmental Engineers, June 1975 (Box 48, Folder 1351)
  - Regional Reports - Delaware River Basin (Draft, Vol. II), Betz Environmental Engineers, June 1975 (Box 48, Folder 1352)
  - Regional Reports - Delaware River Basin (Final Report, Vol. I), Betz Environmental Engineers, September 1975 (Box 48, Folder 1353)
  - Regional Reports - Delaware River Basin (Final Report, Vol. II), Betz Environmental Engineers, September 1975 (Box 48, Folder 1354)
  - Regional Reports - Merrimack-Nashua River Basin (Draft, Vol. I), Abt Associates, June 1975 (Box 49, Folder 1355)
  - Regional Reports - Merrimack-Nashua River Basin (Draft, Vol. II), Abt Associates, June 1975 (Box 49, Folder 1356)
  - Regional Reports - Merrimack-Nashua River Basin (Final Report, Vol. I), Abt Associates, November 1975 (Box 49, Folder 1357)
  - Regional Reports - Merrimack-Nashua River Basin (Final Report, Vol. II), Abt Associates, November 1975 (Box 49, Folder 1358)
  - Regional Reports - Ohio River Basin, Executive Summary (Draft), Dames and Moore, June 1975 (Box 49, Folder 1359)
  - Regional Reports - Ohio River Basin, Vol. I (Draft), Dames and Moore, June 1975 (Box 49, Folder 1360)
  - Regional Reports - Ohio River Basin, Vol. II, Chapters 1-3 (Draft), Dames and Moore, June 1975 (Box 49, Folder 1361)
  - Regional Reports - Ohio River Basin, Vol. II, Chapter 4 (Draft), Dames and Moore, June 1975 (Box 49, Folder 1362)
  - Regional Reports - Ohio River Basin, Vol. II, Chapters 5-7 (Draft), Dames and Moore, June 1975 (Box 49, Folder 1363)
  - Regional Reports - Ohio River Basin, Vol. II, Chapter 8 (Draft), Dames and Moore, June 1975 (Box 49, Folder 1364)
  - Regional Reports - Ohio River Basin, Vol. I, Part I (Final Report), Dames and Moore, November 1975 (Box 49, Folder 1365)
  - Regional Reports - Ohio River Basin, Vol. I, Part II, Chapter 1 (Final Report), Dames and Moore, November 1975 (Box 49, Folder 1366)
  - Regional Reports - Ohio River Basin, Vol. I, Part II, Chapter 2 (Final Report), Dames and Moore, November 1975 (Box 50, Folder 1367)
  - Regional Reports - Ohio River Basin, Vol. I, Part II, Chapter 3 (Final Report), Dames and Moore, November 1975 (Box 50, Folder 1368)
  - Regional Reports - Ohio River Basin, Vol. II, Chapter 4 (Final Report), Dames and Moore, November 1975 (Box 50, Folder 1369)
  - Regional Reports - Ohio River Basin, Vol. II, Chapters 5-6 (Final Report), Dames and Moore, November 1975 (Box 50, Folder 1370)
  - Regional Reports - Ohio River Basin, Vol. II, Chapters 7-8 (Final Report), Dames and Moore, November 1975 (Box 50, Folder 1371)
  - Regional Reports - Lake Erie, Vol. I (Draft), Dalton, Dalton, Little, Newport, June 1975 (Box 50, Folder 1372)
  - Regional Reports - Lake Erie, Vol. II (Draft), Dalton, Dalton, Little, Newport, June 1975 (Box 50, Folder 1373)
  - Regional Reports - Lake Erie, Vol. III (Draft), Dalton, Dalton, Little, Newport, June 1975 (Box 50, Folder 1374)
  - Regional Reports - Lake Erie, (Final Report), Dalton, Dalton, Little, Newport, December 1975 (Box 50, Folder 1375)
  - Regional Reports - Lake Erie, Appendices I-V (Final Report), Dalton, Dalton, Little, Newport, December 1975 (Box 50, Folder 1376)